<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Causality in Cognition Lab</title>
    <link>http://cicl.stanford.edu/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Causality in Cognition Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Tobias Gerstenberg</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cicl.stanford.edu/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Assistant</title>
      <link>http://cicl.stanford.edu/news/undergraduate_assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cicl.stanford.edu/news/undergraduate_assistant/</guid>
      <description>The Causality in Cognition Lab (CICL) is seeking undergraduate research assistants to help us in our investigation of causal cognition! The CICL is a cognitive psychology lab headed by Tobias Gerstenberg. We use a combination of empirical and computational methods to understand how humans reason about cause and effect in the world.
For the fall quarter, research assistants will focus on helping with our causal eyetracking projects. Recent work led by Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the Causality in Cognition Lab!</title>
      <link>http://cicl.stanford.edu/news/lab_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cicl.stanford.edu/news/lab_manager/</guid>
      <description>The Department of Psychology is looking for a full-time Social Science Research Coordinator. This is a one year fixed term position with strong possibility of renewal.
The Causality in Cognition Lab (CICL) studies how the mind learns to represent the causal structure of the world, and how we use this knowledge to predict what will happen, explain what happened, and hold others responsible for the consequences of their actions. In our research, we formalize people&amp;rsquo;s mental models as computational models that yield quantitative predictions about a wide range of situations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>